<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>

        <!--  Report PaperFormat -->
        <record id="paperformat_lease_agreement_report" model="report.paperformat">
            <field name="name">Lease Agreement Report</field>
            <field name="default" eval="True"/>
                <field name="format">A4</field>
                <field name="page_height">0</field>
                <field name="page_width">0</field>
                <field name="orientation">Portrait</field>
                <field name="margin_top">25</field>
                <field name="margin_bottom">20</field>
                <field name="margin_left">7</field>
                <field name="margin_right">7</field>
                <field name="header_line" eval="False"/>
                <field name="header_spacing">20</field>
                <field name="dpi">90</field>
        </record>

        <record id="lease_agreement_report_id" model="ir.actions.report">
            <field name="name">Lease Agreement</field>
            <field name="model">tenancy.details</field>
            <field name="report_type">qweb-pdf</field>
            <field name="report_name">property_management.lease_agreement_qweb_report_template</field>
            <field name="report_file">property_management.lease_agreement_qweb_report_template</field>
            <field name="binding_model_id" ref="property_management.model_tenancy_details"/>
            <field name="binding_type">report</field>
            <field name="print_report_name">'Lease Agreement'</field>
            <field name="paperformat_id" ref="property_management.paperformat_lease_agreement_report"/>
        </record>


        <!-- <template id="lease_agreement_qweb_report_template">
            <t t-call="web.basic_layout">
                <div class="page">
                    <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
                        <div class="page" style="page-break-before: always;">
                            <h2 style="text-align:center">
                                AGREEMENT FOR LEASE
                            </h2>

                            <h4 style="text-align:center;padding-top:110px;">
                                Between
                            </h4>


                            <h2 style="text-align:center;padding-top:110px;">
                                <span><t t-esc="doc.property_landlord_id.name"/></span>
                            </h2>
                            
                            <h5 style="text-align:center;"><span>‘The Landlord’</span></h5>

                            <h4 style="text-align:center;padding-top:110px;">
                                And
                            </h4>

                            <h2 style="text-align:center;padding-top:110px;">
                                <span><t t-esc="doc.tenancy_id.name"/></span>
                            </h2>

                            <h5 style="text-align:center;"><span>‘The Tenant’</span></h5>

                            <div name="company_address" style="padding-top:130px;font-size:18px;">
                                <div>
                                    <span style="text-decoration:underline;font-weight:bold;">Drawn By:</span> 
                                </div>
                                <div>
                                    <t t-esc="doc.property_id.pro_company_id.name"/>
                                </div>
                                <div t-if="doc.property_id.company_id.zip">P.O Box <t t-esc="doc.property_id.company_id.zip"/>,</div>
                                <div t-if="doc.property_id.company_id.street"><t t-esc="doc.property_id.company_id.street"/>.</div>
                            </div>

                            <br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/>
                        </div>

                        <div style="font-size:18px;">
                            <div>
                                <h4 style="text-align:center;text-decoration:underline;">AGREEMENT FOR LEASE OF APARTMENT</h4>
                            </div>

                            <div style="padding-top:10px;">
                                <strong>THIS AGREEMENT</strong> is made at Dar es Salaam this …………………………….. day of ……………………2023
                            </div>

                            <div style="text-align:center;padding-top:15px;font-weight:bold;">
                                <h5>BETWEEN</h5>
                            </div>

                            <div style="padding-top:10px;">
                                <p><strong>M/S <t t-esc="doc.property_landlord_id.name"/></strong>
                                a private limited liability company registered in Tanzania whose registered office is at <b>Plot No</b>.40 Mikocheni Light Industrial Area, Dar es Salaam, and of Post office Box 19716, Dar es salaam, Tanzania. (Hereinafter referred to as ‘the <b>Landlord,</b>’ which expression shall include unless inconsistent with the context the successors and assigns  in title)  of the one part.
                                </p> 
                            </div>

                            <div style="text-align:center;padding-top:15px;font-weight:bold;">
                                <h5>AND</h5>
                            </div>

                            <div style="padding-top:10px;">
                                <p>
                                    <strong><t t-esc="doc.tenancy_id.name"/></strong>,of <b>P.O Box No:<t t-esc="doc.tenancy_id.zip"/> <t t-esc="doc.tenancy_id.street"/>, <t t-esc="doc.tenancy_id.country_id.name"/></b>.(Hereinafter referred to as ‘the <b>  Tenant,</b>’ which expression shall include unless inconsistent with the context the successors and assigns in title) of the other part.    
                                </p>
                            </div>

                            <div style="padding-top:15px;font-weight:bold;">
                                <h5>WHEREAS</h5>
                            </div>

                            <div style="margin-left:25px;">
                                <p>
                                    The <b>Landlord</b> being a developer is the owner in occupation of a building with Flat Apartments on Plot No. <b><t t-esc="doc.property_id.plot_no"/> <t t-esc="doc.property_id.street"/></b> together with all the unexhausted improvements, developments and appurtenances therein contained (herein after referred to as ‘the <b>Property</b>’).    
                                </p>

                                <p>
                                    The Landlord has offered to lease a flat apartment No <b><t t-esc="doc.property_id.room_no"/></b> of Tower <b><t t-esc="doc.property_id.no_of_towers"/></b> on the <b><t t-esc="doc.property_id.floor"/></b> floor of the Property (herein after referred to as the ‘<b>Demised Premises</b>’) and the Tenant has agreed to enter into a lease agreement of the said Demised Premises subject to the herein below undertaking.
                                </p>
                            </div>

                            <div style="padding-top:10px;">
                                <p>Now this Agreement Witnesseth As follows:</p>
                                <p> Operative Provisions:</p>
                                <p> 1. Definations and Interpretation</p>
                                <div style="margin-left:20px;">
                                    <p>(a)Definitions and Interpretation</p>
                                    <div style="margin-left:20px;">
                                        <p>(i)In this Agreement if the Context so allows:</p>
                                        <p>‘<b>Agreement</b>’ means this Lease Agreement, rules and regulations, annextures and includes any amendment or other novation agreed and duly signed and executed by the parties in accordance with the terms of this Agreement.</p>
                                        <p>‘<b>Co-Owners</b>’ means the other occupiers either by rent or purchase of the flat apartments in the Property.</p>

                                        <p>‘<b>Common area</b>’ means whole or a portion of property that is used by all co- owners for their common use.</p>

                                        <p>‘<b>Demised Premise</b>’ means the flat apartment offered to the Tenant as it is and basis and includes the parking lot allocated.</p>

                                        <p>‘<b>Encumbrance</b>’ means any mortgage, charge, pledge, lien, assignment, hypothecation, preferential right or trust, arrangement or other encumbrance, security, agreement or arrangement of any kind or any right conferring a priority of payment affecting the title to the property.</p>

                                        <p>‘<b>Management</b>’ means the estate manager incharge of the day to day management of the common property.</p>

                                        <p>‘<b>Monthly service charges</b>’ means the charges made on items listed on annexure A1 only.</p>

                                        <p>‘<b>Property</b>’ means Part of all the piece of land known as Plot no’s 
                                        <b><t t-esc="doc.property_id.plot_no"/> <t t-esc="doc.property_id.street"/></b>, together with the storeway building where the Demised Premises is part of the flat apartment.</p>

                                        <p>‘<b>Security Deposit</b>’ means an amount deposited by the Tenant to the Landlord as security for any damages or defaults, its refundable at the termination of the Lease Agreement in accordance with the Tenants covenants and obligations.</p>

                                        <p>‘<b>Vendor</b>’ means the seller of the Demised premise and Landlord.</p>
                                    </div>

                                    <p>
                                        (b) Words of one gender include both other genders, and entities, and words denoting natural persons include corporations and firms.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>
                                        (c) Words denoting an obligation on a party to do any acts, matter or thing include an obligation to procure that it be done, and words placing a party under a restriction include an obligation not to permit infringement of the restriction.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>
                                        (d) Where the Tenant comprises two or more parties, the obligations of the Tenant are in relation to each such party joint and several.
                                    </p>
                                    <p>
                                        (e) Reference to ‘liability’ include where the context so allows, claims, demands, proceedings, damages, costs and expenses.
                                    </p>
                                </div>  
                            </div>

                            <div style="padding-top:10px;">
                                <p>NOW THIS Agreement Witnesseth as follows:</p>
                                <div style="margin-left:20px;">
                                    <p>1. Lease</p>
                                    <div style="margin-left:20px;">
                                        <p>
                                            In pursuance of the said Agreement and in Consideration of the rent hereby reserved and the Tenant’s Covenants hereinafter mentioned, the Landlord hereby demises unto the Tenant the Demised Premises for a period of <b><t t-esc="doc.duration_id.duration"/></b> Commencing on The  <b><t t-esc="doc.start_date.strftime('%d/%B/%Y')"/></b>, and ending on  <b><t t-esc="doc.end_date.strftime('%d/%B/%Y')"/></b>, subject to renew on terms and conditions as hereunder.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>

                                    <p>2. Payment of the Rent.</p>
                                    <div style="margin-left:20px;">
                                        <p><b>(i)</b>  The rent herein reserved shall be  <b><t t-esc="doc.property_id.currency_id.full_name"/>. <span t-esc="doc.property_id.currency_id.with_context(lang='en').amount_to_text(doc.property_id.tenancy_price)"/>. (<t t-esc="doc.property_id.currency_id.name"/> <t t-esc="doc.property_id.tenancy_price"/> /- only)  <t t-esc="doc.property_id.rent_unit"/></b>, to be paid three months in advance amounting to total amount of USD. Four Thousand Nine Hundred Fifty Only. (USD 4,950/- Only) + VAT (If Applicable). The said rental amount must be paid timely as agreed and any late payment shall attract a monthly interest rate of <b><t t-esc="doc.monthly_interest_rate"/> % </b>
                                        of monthly rent on each month of delay.
                                        </p>

                                        <p><b>(ii)</b>  The Tenant shall be responsible for payment of stamp duty on this Lease Agreement and its Counterpart,
                                        </p>

                                        <p><b>(iii)</b>  Tenant shall deduct the Withholding Tax at the prevailing rate (Presently <b><t t-esc="doc.presently_rate"/> % </b>) as required under section 82 of Income Tax Act and must produce to the Landlord the Withholding Certificate in the manner prescribed under Sec. 85 of Income Tax Act with proof of payment.
                                        </p>

                                        <p>
                                           For claiming this withholding tax, Landlord has every right to ensure that Tenant has made the payment of Withholding Tax to the Tanzania Revenue Authority. 
                                        </p>

                                        <p>
                                            For avoidance of doubt, the Tenant must provide the Withholding Tax Certificate and proof of payment within thirty days from the end of the month in which deduction is made, failure of which the landlord shall exercise his powers and recover the same amount from the Tenant
                                        </p>

                                        <p><b>(iv)</b>  Value Added Tax (VAT), is to be added. </p>

                                        <p><b>(v)</b>  To pay the monthly service charge as per the Property management contract entered by the parties and the estate management as part of this agreement. </p>

                                        <p><b>(vi)</b>  The service charges and other costs/reimbursable must be paid timely and any default shall amount to penalties not limited to termination of the lease agreement upon issuing a default notice to the Tenant.
                                        </p>

                                        <p><b>(vii)</b>  Any late payments of service charges and utility charges shall amount to disconnection/discontinue of the Services offered by the Property manager upon issuing a seventy-two (72) hours default notice.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>

                                    <p>3. Landlord’s Warranties and Representations.</p>
                                    <div style="margin-left:20px;">
                                        <p>
                                            The Landlord warrants and represents to the Tenant that it is the legal owner in possession of the property herein and that it is legally capable and duly authorized to enter into this lease agreement and perform all the obligations set out herein.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>

                                    <p>4. Tenant’s Rights and Obligations.</p>
                                    <div style="margin-left:20px;">
                                        <p>
                                            The Tenant hereby covenant with the Landlord as follows:
                                            <b>4.1</b> To pay the monthly Rent in advance as agreed in clause 2 of this agreement.
                                        </p>

                                        <p><b>4.2</b> To pay the service charges in advance and on timely basis.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.3</b> To pay all fees and all rates and charges for use of water from Dawasco or any other body that may be in force, electricity from Tanesco or any other power generating body that may be in force in respect of demised premises during the said lease period.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.3.1</b> Failure to comply with the payments of such services shall amount to disconnection of the services for the entire period and any late payments shall be made with interests and penalties.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.4</b> At all times to keep the interior of the demised premises and the appurtenances thereof including doors, windows and other fixtures, fittings, fastening, electrical wires, water drains, water fittings and other pipes and paintings and decorations thereof in  substantial routine repair and good condition.
                                        </p>

                                        <p><b>4.5</b> To keep the surrounding ground of the demised premises in good order and condition.
                                        </p>

                                        <p><b>4.6</b> To use the demised premises for residential purposes only and maintain a high moral ethical standards.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.7</b> To permit the Landlord and or his agents with or without workmen at all reasonable times during day time by prior appointment to enter upon the demised premises for the purpose of viewing and executing any repair necessary under the covenants herein contained.
                                        </p>

                                        <p><b>4.8</b> Not to make any alterations or additions to the demised premises without first obtaining the written consent of the Landlord.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.9</b> Not to assign or sublet or part with the possession of the demised premises or any part thereof without the written consent of the Landlord, PROVIDED ALWAYS that the occupation of the demised premises or any part thereof by any person in the service or employment of the Tenant shall not constitute an assignment, underlies or parting with the possession of the demised premises or any part thereof.</p>

                                        <p>
                                            Incase  the  Tenant  decides  to  sub-lease,  the  terms  and  conditions  of  this  lease agreement together with the rules and regulations must be followed.
                                        </p>

                                        <p><b>4.10</b> Not to use the demised premises in a way that would create annoyance, disturbance, public/private threat, nuisance or any danger to the public, neighbours or other Tenants.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.11</b> Persons of indecent character such as prostitutes, drug dealers or use of the Demised premise as a brothel is strictly not allowed in the Demised premises such an act shall amount to immediate termination of this Agreement.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.12</b> To insure and keep insured himself, family, employees, his invitees and all his/ their personal belongings both in the demised premises and the Common  Area against loss or damage by fire and any other risks.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.13</b> To indemnify the Landlord for any loss that he may sustain as a result of failure by the Tenant to maintain adequate insurance for its property.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.14</b> The Landlord shall not be responsible for any damage, theft or loss whatsoever involving the Tenant’s properties/belongings as the security shall be the responsibility of the Tenant.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.15</b> The Tenant shall provide adequate security for the property and all goods kept on the demised premise including his parking place, Tenant agrees that the Landlord SHALL not be liable in any way whatsoever, for any theft or loss on the demised premise during the entire lease period.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.16</b> That the Tenants hereby agrees that any domestic workers/house help whose engaged to offer services to the tenants, and who resides outside the premises shall be subjected to the inspection by the security guard during the reporting time and departing/leaving time at the entrance/exit gate.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.17</b> On the expiration or sooner after termination of the term hereby granted, to deliver up the demised premises to the Landlord in good tenable condition and leave all the fixtures and furniture’s of the property intact and having been repaired reasonable wear and tear excepted.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.18</b> Tenant shall also  pay  to  Landlord  a  “<b>Security  Deposit</b>”  of  <b><t t-esc="doc.currency_id.symbol"/><t t-esc="doc.security_deposite"/></b>.  <t t-esc="deposit_amount"/>/- as security for any damages or defaults.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.19</b> Should any damage, breakage or non-repair on the demised premises occur and the Tenant fails to make good of the same, the Landlord shall assess the costs of such damages and thereby notify the Tenant to make good of the same, failure of which the Landlord shall use the security deposit to repair or replace the items.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.20</b> To pay for the fuel consumption of the generator used when electricity from the national grid is interrupted on a pro-rata basis or basing on metric basis and upon issuance of a reasonable notice from the Landlord, failure of which amounts to the breach of this agreement and disconnection of the services.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.21</b> That the Tenant, his agents, associates, sub lessees and any other occupiers of the demised premises shall abide to the rules and regulations of the demised premises and apartments failure of which shall led to the breach of this contract and the Landlord’s entitlement to remedies.</p>

                                        <p><b>4.22</b> That the Tenant has to read, understand and observe the rules and regulations herein attached to be read together with this agreement.</p>
                                    </div>

                                    <p>5. Landlord’s rights and obligations.</p>
                                    <div style="margin-left:20px;">
                                        <p><b>5.1</b> During the subsistence of this agreement not to sell, assign, transfer, lease, sublet or otherwise dispose and deal with the demised premises in a manner prejudicial to the Tenant’s rights contained under this agreement.</p>

                                        <p><b>5.2</b> During the subsistence of the lease, the Landlord will be responsible for payment of property tax and all the site rates, land rent or other statutory charges and impositions levied in respect of the Demised Premise to the property owners by the government during the currency of the said term.</p>

                                        <p><b>5.3</b> To permit the Tenant hereby observing and performing the agreed covenants to peacefully posses the demised premises during the lease period.</p>

                                        <p><b>5.4</b> To provide the Tenant a parking place for only one car which shall only be used for parking the Tenant’s car only, the allocated parking shall not be used for any other purposes other than parking the Tenant’s car.</p>

                                        <div style="margin-left:20px;">
                                            <p><b>5.5.1</b> The parking is restricted to the labelled one and not otherwise.</p>

                                            <p><b>5.5.2</b> Any obstruction or wrong parking shall amount to trespass with consequences as stayed in the rules and regulation.</p>

                                            <p><b>5.5.3</b> Parking allocated shall be at car owner’s risk and not the liability of the Landlord or the management.</p>

                                            <p><b>5.5.4</b> No services or maintenance of the Tenant’s vehicle in the property and in the parking area unless it is an emergency cases which must be reported to the Property manager.</p>
                                        </div>

                                        <p><b>5.5</b> If at any time the demised premises are rendered unfit for use by accidental fire or other causes beyond the control of the Tenant, the Landlord shall allow the Tenant an abatement of all or part of the said rent proportionate to the existence and duration of the damage until the demised premises shall be fit for use again.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <p>6. PROVIDED ALWAYS and it is hereby agreed and declared that.</p>
                                    <div style="margin-left:20px;">
                                        <p><b>6.1</b> In the event the Tenant fails to fulfil any of its obligations under this lease, and where this lease specifically provides no other remedy for such failure, the Landlord shall give the Tenant notice in writing to remedy the breach within a period of not less than fourteen (14) days. If upon such notice, the Tenant fails to remedy the default, the Landlord will be entitled to issue thirty (30) days notice of termination of the lease.</p>

                                        <p>Upon such termination, the Landlord shall refund to the Tenant any Rent received in advance for an unexpired period of the Lease, without interests and after deducting one month’s rent as notice of default and all taxes paid and costs for any damages assessed by the Parties.</p>

                                        <p><b>6.2</b> If and whenever during the said lease period the said rent or any part thereof shall be unpaid for 30 days after the date due for payment and if any covenant on the Tenants part herein contained shall not be performed or observed then in any of the said cases it shall be lawful for the Landlord at any time thereafter to re-enter upon the property or any part thereof and then  this  lease  agreement  shall  absolutely  determine  without  prejudice to  any  rights  or remedies which may have accrued to either party against the other in respect of antecedent breach of any of the covenants herein contained and the Landlord shall have the right to take any legal action in recovery of any rent due and accruing.</p>

                                        <p><b>6.3</b>The Tenant and the Landlord shall renew this Lease Agreement by giving each other a written notice of thirty days before the expiration of lease period in terms granted herein expressing their intention to agree to the terms and conditions of the renewed lease period. If the parties agree, the renewed lease period shall commence immediately upon the expiration of the current lease period.</p>

                                        <p><b>6.4</b> (i)Either Party may by giving thirty (30) days written notice assigning reasons, terminate this agreement, reasons which should not be unreasonably withheld and any advance amount paid for the unexpired period of the Lease shall be refunded after deducting all the taxes paid and any damages assessed.</p>

                                        <p>Any termination by the Tenant before the expiry of the Lease period without giving thirty days’ notice shall amount to deduction by the Landlord of one month’s rent from the security deposit or one month’s rent deduction from any rent paid for the unexpired period in lieu of the notice.</p>

                                        <p><b>6.4</b> (ii)Incase of the Tenant’s premature termination of the  lease  agreement  before  the expiry of the first Six months or before quarter of the period of the Lease Agreement, advance rent paid for first six months or quarter of the period of the Lease Agreement shall not be refundable.</p>

                                        <p><b>6.5</b> (i)At the time of termination or at the expiry (maturity) of the lease agreement, The keys and all other properties of the landlord MUST be handed over to the duly authorized property Manager.</p>

                                        <p><b>6.5</b> (ii)Any delay in the handing over of the key shall amount to penalty which shall attract an amount equivalent to one month’s lease.</p>

                                        <p><b>6.5</b> (iii)Upon handing over of the keys or within thirty days before the expiry or termination of the contract a formal inspection of the demised premises shall be done in presence of both the tenant and property manager, Any damages shall be assessed and its only after a formal clearance by the property management that the Tenant shall be allowed to move his/her properties.</p>

                                        <p><b>6.6</b> Any notice under this lease agreement shall be in writing and any notice to the Tenant shall be sufficiently served if left addressed to him on the demised premises or served to him by registered post and any notice to the Landlord shall be sufficiently served if sent to him by registered post addressed to it at its usual place of business.</p>

                                        <p><b>6.7</b> Recreation areas and facilities on the third floor of the said building shall be reserved for the members only upon registration.</p>
                                    </div>

                                    <p>7. Dispute Resolution.</p>
                                    <div style="margin-left:20px;">
                                        <p>This Agreement shall be construed and governed by the Laws of Tanzania and any dispute, difference arising out of or in connection with this Agreement shall be amicably mediated between the parties within thirty days from the occurrence of the dispute. Failure of which the matter shall be referred to the court of competent jurisdiction with in the united republic of Tanzania.</p>
                                    </div>

                                    <p><b>IN WITNESS WHEREOF</b> the parties hereto have duly executed these presents in the manner and on the day and year hereinafter appearing.</p>


                                    <p>Dated at Dar es Salaam this .............day of ............... 2023</p>

                                    <div style="padding-top:10px;">
                                        <div class="row">
                                            <div class="col-6 text-left">
                                                <p>
                                                    <b>SEALED</b> with the <b>Common Seal</b> of the said 
                                                    <b>M/S <span><t t-esc="doc.property_landlord_id.name"/></span></b>. and DELIVERED in presence of us this………..……………day of………………………2023
                                                </p>
                                            </div>
                                            <div class="col-2 text-left"/>
                                            <div class="col-4 text-right">
                                                    <div class="text-center">_______________________</div>
                                                    <div class="text-center" style="font-weight:bold;padding-top:5px;">LANDLORD</div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>

                                        <div class="row" style="font-weight:bold;padding-top:20px;">
                                            <div class="col-6">
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Signature: ………………………………………………
                                                </div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Full Name: ………………………………………………</div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Address: ………………………………………………</div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Qualification: ………………………………………………</div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>

                                        <div class="row" style="font-weight:bold;padding-top:20px;">
                                            <div class="col-6">
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Signature: ………………………………………………</div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Full Name: ………………………………………………</div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Address: ………………………………………………</div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Qualification: ………………………………………………</div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>

                                    <div style="padding-top:15px;">
                                        <div class="row">
                                            <div class="col-6 text-left" style="padding-top:20px;">
                                                <p>
                                                    <b>SEALED</b> with the <b>Common Seal</b> of the said 
                                                    <b>M/S <span><t t-esc="doc.tenancy_id.name"/></span></b>. and DELIVERED in presence of us this………..……………day of………………………2023
                                                </p>
                                            </div>
                                            <div class="col-2 text-left"/>
                                            <div class="col-4 text-right">
                                                    <div class="text-center">_______________________</div>
                                                    <div class="text-center" style="font-weight:bold;padding-top:5px;">TENANT</div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>

                                        <div class="row" style="font-weight:bold;padding-top:20px;">
                                            <div class="col-6">
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Signature: ………………………………………………</div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Full Name: ………………………………………………</div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Address: ………………………………………………</div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Qualification: ………………………………………………</div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>

                                        <div class="row" style="font-weight:bold;padding-top:20px;">
                                            <div class="col-6">
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Signature: ………………………………………………</div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Full Name: ………………………………………………</div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Address: ………………………………………………</div>
                                                <div style="padding-top:5px;">Qualification: ………………………………………………</div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>

                        </div>
                    </t>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template> -->


        <template id="lease_agreement_qweb_report_template">
            <t t-call="web.basic_layout">
                <div class="page">
                    <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
                        <div>
                            <span><t t-esc="doc.contract_terms"/></span>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>